[{"answer": "I think its meaning is clear", "docId": "Hannibal.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "That could be", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You want to get married...", "docId": "Hannibal.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You're ready now", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "And who is", "docId": "Hannibal.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "...the whole world's out to get you..", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Try my friend", "docId": "Hannibal.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "He was the orderly, during Dr. my friend's stay in Prison", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "How do you think that made him feel?  ,", "docId": "Hannibal.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "an orphan", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " my friend, curator of the my friend, 2 months missing", "docId": "Hannibal.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Somewhere where his family are offering a thirty grand reward for Information, so on", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "...\", \"dependency_gramma", "docId": "Hannibal.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "A reward..", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What're they on about", "docId": "Hannibal.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Speaking of the Vacant Post", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Ah, Barne", "docId": "Hannibal.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I have not read you your rights", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "He said, and these were his words, he our time together, because I was civil", "docId": "Hannibal.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "He told me, he preferred to Eat the Rude. O", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "...constant humiliation.  And why", "docId": "Hannibal.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "....because we don't have any mmm..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I want the money", "docId": "Hannibal.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "The shape of a Three", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "that place.  Go.  Affirmative.  Okay, Happiness is a Green Light.  We've got my friend in the kitchen, cooking.  The dope's D.E.A.  want her on that place of some firecrackers.  Starlin", "docId": "Hannibal.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "...these guy'll back you up", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Ah, Commendatore... you, too, admire my friend", "docId": "Hannibal.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "If such there breathe, I'm sure you could  him...  Your reputation does you honor.", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "...and my need for The Institution..", "docId": "Hannibal.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "And how did he do that", "qsentId": 30}]